

PYTHON · DIANGO DEVELOPER

Tehran Iran

🛮 (+98) 918-362-0574 | 🗷 r.dehghani.90@gmail.com | 🌴 www.dariush-dehghani.ir | 🖸 r-dehghani | 🛅 rouhollah-dehghani

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary

Current Python and Django developer at start-up company based in Netherlands. 2+ years experience specializing in the backend development. Someone who loves Linux and Python. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience

Code Team Academy

Tehran, Iran

Jan 2021 - Present

PYTHON AND DJANGO DEVELOPER

• Design and Development Online learning platform codebezanim.ir

Utilized Docker coupled with Traefik as a reverse-proxy and a load-balancer to achieve Continuous Delivery goal on high scalable environment Nexus, Orchestrated Docker Container using docker-compose, Setting up Continuous Integration(CI) and Continuous Delivery (CD) Pipelines using GitLabCi, Django and python, Setting up Nginx web-server to serve and cache static content, Having the role of Application Administrator due to an extensive knowledge of Linux operating system

Tehran, Iran

PYTHON AND DJANGO DEVELOPER INTERN

Jan. 2021 - Present

- Design and Development Conditional Order and Order Book, Containerized Using Docker. (Services: Matching engine, Stock information consumer service connected to the RabbitMQ, Triggers management by end-user, Email notification)
- Logging Activities Application Using Python and Django. (Services: Django application hosted with user authentications and activity logging features)
- Django Application for Online Learning and Teaching Marketplace. (Services: Django application with users authentication, Article management and online classes registration)

Education

Arak University

Arak, Iran

M.S. STRUCTURAL ENGINEERING AND B.S. IN CIVIL ENGINEERING

Oct. 2012 - Oct. 2014

Skills_

Python, Numpy, Pandas, Seaborn, Matplotlib, Django, Django REST framework, Git, Linux, GitHub

Certificates

- Git and GitHub Essentials ☑
- Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) □
- Certificate of completion for terminal bash vim essentials □

Languages_

English

FLUENT IN SPEAKING AND PROFICIENT IN RESEARCH

Persion

NATIVE